YASMINE SOUISSI

Instructor FullStack JS

Menzah 7 BIS, Ariana, 2038, Ariana | +216 24 422 552 | yasminesouissi852@gmail.com

Profil Professionnel

Autonomous and enthusiastic, my first experiences allowed me to strengthen my skills and understand the different tools and techniques of Web Development.

Compétences

- Time Management
- Team work
- Communication
- React JS
- Node JS

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- C/C++
- QT Creator
- SQL/NO SQL

Parcours professionnel

Community Manager 09/2021 - Actuel

MAG'S GYM - Ariana

- Reviewing and replying to comments left on social networks.
- Interacting with community members on internal platforms.
- Encourage user debate with recently published content.
- Gathering and recording customer feedback.
- Creating relevant and engaging content.
- Brainstorm content ideas for posts that week (both social media and blog posts). It has to be original content that adds value to their community.

Instructor FullStack JS 08/2021 - Actuel

GOMYCODE – Ariana

- Weekly follow-ups and Mentoring of students
- Organize workshops and validate checkpoints.
- Ensure monthly evaluation interviews with students.
- Ensure weekly standup with students.
- Make learning fun for our students.
- Commit to make students the Best Version of themselves.
- Teach how to find solutions and not the solutions.
- Encourage students to Learn by making.

Formation

Software Engineering ESPRIT - Ghazella, Ariana	09/2020 – En cours
FullStack JS	01/2021 - 06/2021
GOMYCODE - Lac 1	
Graphic Design	11/2020 - 01/2021
MasterClass - Bardo , Danden	
Baccalaureat: Technologic	09/2019 – 06/2020
Les Péres Blanc - Tunis 1	
General Baccalaureat : Scientific	09/2017 - 07/2019
Gustave Flaubert - Marsa	

Langues

Français	Anglais
Avancé (C1)	Intermédiaire supérieur (B2)
Centres d'intérêt	

- Sport
 - Musique
 - Lecture
- Cinéma